# **CURRICULUM VITAE**

# Firly Taufikurohman

Backend Developer | Data Scientist

## **CONTACT**

Phone : (+62) 895-6405-70172 Email : ftaufikrr@gmail.com

Linkedin : https://www.linkedin.com/in/firly-taufikurohman-6bb857114

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a fresh graduate of the National Institute of Technology. I have two years of experience in web development, which I gained during my time at university. Furthermore, I studied deep learning for my final project in university. Currently, I am highly interested in deep learning and web development, particularly in backend development.

#### **EDUCATION**

# • NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, BANDUNG

Aug 2018 - Aug 2023

Bachelor's Degree, Informatics Engineering

GPA: 3.78

## • SMA NEGERI 18 KOTA BANDUNG

2015 - 2018

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## • BACKEND DEVELOPER

BLAZER INDONESIA CLUB, FREELANCE

Nov 2022 – Feb 2023, Remote

Developed and migrated the technology used in the BIC application API to Codeigniter4 and MongoDB for the database.

# • FULL STACK PHP DEVELOPER

PT. TELKOM AKSES, INTERNSHIP

Jul 2021 - Sep 2021, Hybrid

Working as an internship program organized by National Institute of Technology. Developed a content management system for organizing company data and calculation data using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and CodeIgniter 4 in model view controller pattern.

## **PROJECTS**

# • DEEP LEARNING ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE CLASSIFICATION

NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, FINAL PROJECT

Feb 2023 - Aug 2023

Created and implemented a deep learning model that classified the severity of Alzheimer's disease based on MRI scan images, using Keras library with EfficientNetB3 and EfficientNetV2S architectures, also Flask framework to implement the model into a website.

# **SKILLS**

• **Programming Language**: NodeJS, PHP, Python, C#

• Framework: ExpressJS, CodeIgniter4, Flask

• CSS: Bootstrap, Tailwind

• Database: MySQL, MongoDB

API Documentation: PostmanAuthentication: JSON Web Tokens

• Containerization: Docker

# **CERTIFICATION**

- Certificate Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Back-End untuk Pemula, Dicoding, May 2024
- Certificate Cloud Practitioner Essentials (Belajar Dasar AWS Cloud), Dicoding, 2024
- Certificate Belajar Machine Learning untuk Pemula, Dicoding, 2023
- Certificate Belajar Dasar Visualisasi Data, Dicoding, 2023
- Certificate Memulai Pemrograman dengan Python, Dicoding, 2023
- Certificate Belajar Pemrograman SOLID, Dicoding, 2022